Where am I?
I did?
You gave them false data
so that Salem could get away.
Perfectly logical.
Your analysis concluded.
That's what I would want.
My lord's slain.
What is it?
There's a firefight taking place in the hangar.
A team of assassins?
No, my lord. It's the UFE in Princess of Salem.
I will cover you.
Now run!
Eliminate all of those Terrans, now!
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
Emergency launch, now.
That is not safe, my lord. There is a battle out there.
And one inside, too.
Get us away from all combat zones at full emergency speed.
Take cover!
Come back, your highness.
Inca, where is Princess of Salem?
Still no word from her.
Then she... didn't escape with you? Hold on.
Mission is still complete. Inca, come pick me up, okay?
No!
You are alone with your hand If it hasn't reefs, we're not to dig -,
It's not running away drows Evans.
Okay!
Oh
as a foreign patch...
The dream in the beginning...
There's no time,
Chapter 7 in the present,
The zero fades on its path.
Your front seat reaches the distance which lets around.
It inspires give you a series of wild facts.
My sincere apologies, Lord Plonkane. I am sorry to involve you.
Not at all. Your safety is part of my mission.
Your mission?
Yes. My orders to come here were received from his majesty himself.
Grandfather sent you?
The Emperor felt great concern.
Misgivings over conquering the Earth's system following the death of Count Sosbom.
So I was ordered to study the situation, and to personally ensure your safety.
It's imperative I speak to my grandfather at once.
It is possible to make contact. However...
Lord Plonkane, a transmission from the moon base.
Put it through.
My Lord Plonkane, may I ask where you are taking Princess of Salem?
My dear Count Troiard, I am simply evacuating her to a place of safety.
The moon base is a fortified location. There is no place where her highness would be more safe.
And yet, a battle was taking place there.
You may rest assured, the enemy has already been eliminated. Please, return at once.
I will not go back to you there!
While on Earth, I watched birds as they flew.
Yes, your highness.
The Earth was recovering. The world of man and nature coexisting.
You were the one who was teaching that to me.
That humans and nature...
That Earth in verse...
Could live and prosper together!
Yes, you are correct.
I was the one who said that.
Stygia's squadron has been dispatched to pursue them.
Seize that ship on sight.
I'm begging you, Slane.
If you care for me at all, stop this war.
Please, make peace with Earth.
Very well.
Perhaps you're right.
Why don't you come back so that we can all discuss it?
Oh, Slane.
That sector is very dangerous.
Please return at once.
Lord Plonkane, you will turn back immediately.
I am afraid not.
I'm sorry, but I have orders from Princess Asalem.
Stealth mode to maximum, now!
Yes, my lord.
Lord Plonkane's spaceship, the Hadriacus, has vanished.
Continue searching.
Yes, my lord.
For the time being, we won't have to worry about pursuit.
You have my gratitude.
Tell me, what am I to do now?
Well, Earth's military is pursuing me.
And all the orbital knights are backing Slane.
I must somehow make contact with the crew of the Deucalion.
But, m'lady, there is one knight we know to be on your side.
The knight who brought you the message from Inaho Kaisuka.
Count Mazurek.
Now I can demonstrate my loyalty to Her Highness, Princess Asalem.
Landing castle, lift off!
Lysdale leader to all units.
Take the targets off the starboard bow.
Don't let them get close to the Deucalion.
Enemy formation closing 3 o'clock.
6-0 elevation angle.
Increase starboard AA cannon fire.
Dispatch from headquarters.
Orders to withdraw, captain.
Draw now?
I guess they must have gotten the results they were after.
Results, ma'am?
The real operation that we were only decoys for.
Prepare to withdraw.
All units return to base.
Ma'am, most tanks 0-0 and 1-1 are closing in.
On course for return.
Ingo, Inaho made it back.
They're cleared for docking.
Get them on board ASAP.
That was easy.
Seems they were no match for us.
Too easy.
What are they up to?
Count Troiard, the UFE is withdrawing from the battle.
Shall we pursue?
No.
All units return to base.
They will rearm for the next offensive.
Also, I want my landing castle brought in to defend the moon base.
Yes, my lord.
Is that something that belonged to my sister?
Princess Lemrina.
Did she escape?
So, will I ever see her again?
Yes.
That you can count on.
I do feel...
Sorry for her.
And for you.
Inaho.
What is young Kaizuka's condition?
Nothing life-threatening at this point.
But still, his cranial nerves are under quite a strain from the analytical engine.
I told him not to, but you can see how much he's let its domain expand.
What does that mean, doctor?
Inaho has given the machine a part of his brain.
Damn crazy kid.
I need some way that I can bring this war to an end.
I will directly address all of the Orbital Knights.
With all due respect, that would not prove sufficient.
Why would you say that?
From the beginning of hostilities decades ago, the Orbital Knights have been waiting to take the Earth.
With that false royal proclamation, Count Troyard has given them a license to do so.
He has unified them with promises of great status in the New Kingdom, as well as Alt-Noah activation.
But the strongest factor was that announcement of betrothal to you.
You would have no credibility if you simply said to end it now.
As long as your sister is at his side pretending to be you.
Oh, Princess Isalem, it is wonderful to see you looking so well.
Thank you for your assistance.
It is so kind of you.
More credit than I deserve.
Though I must say, your highness, I am relieved at being able to repay my debt.
Your debt?
Yes.
To the Terran boy.
Inaho Kaizuka.
I've seen reports that a part of your force went to the moon base.
Would you mind explaining why, Captain Mogbarich?
Game time call, sir.
If we were to lose the princess now, we would also lose any chance at peace permanently.
What are you saying, Captain?
The voice and face of the enemy is not the real Princess Isalem.
We have no evidence whatsoever for that.
Which does not change the truth, sir.
We have confirmed the launch of Mazurek Castle.
It is said that right before Count Mazurek escaped and fled, he was visited by one of your crew.
Yes, that is correct, sir.
And your point?
Once again, one of your troops was in the area.
What a coincidence.
Quite remarkable, indeed.
Soon, the Earth and the Moon will be in proximity again.
The landing castle stationed on the satellite belt will reinforce moon base defenses.
We need to set a few things straight before that happens.
So I will now give you a new mission.
We will gather our combined forces and launch an all-out attack on the moon base.
The Deucalion will spearhead the attack.
Yes, sir.
I will relay details later.
Good luck, Captain.
He hates us more than anyone could.
Not possible.
Because I'm the one who hates him even more.
Why would Slane start a war?
And bring such destruction?
Oh, m'lady.
The Slane I knew was so kind.
Adored nature.
He truly loved the Earth.
The wondrous things he found there.
He was not someone who entertained such pointless conflict.
How could he have done this?
Your Highness, Lord Slane has not changed at all deep down.
I do not know if the things Lord Slane has done are right or wrong.
But he has always cared deeply for you and kept you alive in his heart.
He has only wanted whatever it was that would be best for you,
even if he thought it might jeopardize his life.
And always believing that you would awaken one day.
Yes, I have seen that.
Thank you for reminding me, Adel Ritzo.
So will you be able to make contact with Verse?
Yes.
However, understand that His Majesty may be...
We cannot afford to stop at half measures now.
My Lord Clonkane, I now require your assistance.
I need to use your ship's audience chamber.
Yes, Princess Asalem.
It shall be as you say.
Attention all forces.
Operations scheduled to commence at 1500 hours UTC.
Man battle stations.
Stand by.
Lieutenant Marito.
Headed off to battle, huh?
Well, yeah.
I'd hope to not go back with you again, Doc.
I'm sorry we didn't get the chance.
That doesn't sound like you.
Well, it's a low-pressure environment, and I don't want to make myself sick.
No, I didn't mean that.
This won't be our last chance.
Yeah, when I'm back.
So, this is one of those final showdown kind of deals?
I guess so.
If we finish him off, wouldn't it be?
If somebody dies in action, I'd call that final, wouldn't you?
Hey!
Come on, man.
Don't jinx us, okay?
Yeah, he's right, you know.
All of us are gonna make it back in one piece.
My lord slain.
The UFE has begun to mass its forces.
How shall we proceed?
As usual.
We launch all forces and we intercept the UFE.
And in the meantime, we request assistance from the Orbital Knights who back us.
Assistant, sir?
This offensive is for the entire Earth.
Now the Terrans will know how it feels to have no home to return to.
Now!
Oh, Yuki.
Now, do you feel okay?
Yeah.
I'm so glad.
You did really good today.
Take it easy for a while.
He's going to attack.
Everything.
Is it almost time for the mission?
Stay in bed.
Don't even think about going anywhere.
I'm sorry, Yuki.
Something's come up that I have to take care of.
You can't now!
Yuki, please.
Let me go.
There's the face that says no matter what, you're going.
And you know what else?
Here's the voice that says I'm stubborn, so just give in.
Damn it, all right.
But when you return, we'll have dinner together.
That's a death sentence if I ever heard one.
Hey, you!
You're not allowed to talk like that.
You come back alive, and that's a big sister order.
You too, Yuki.
Hey, Naho.
You feeling a little better now?
Is this it?
Oh, yeah.
The Sleipnir Final Showdown custom job.
Sure you don't think that payload's a bit much?
Getting close enough to use this stuff in a space battle, you'd have to be nuts.
Looks like things are going to get a little nuts.
What do you mean by that?
He's not taking this seriously.
Inko.
Why is it boys always have to be this way?
Hey, Naho, you're in no condition to go into battle, and you know it.
Why don't you let us handle this one?
Because I can't.
Well, why not?
Do you think you're some kind of hotshot ace and no one else is as special as you?
I promise you, I've never thought about myself that way.
Darn it, Naho!
Why can't you just understand?
Go out this time, and there's a good chance you won't make it back again.
Please, Naho.
We may not have another miracle again like last time.
I don't want to.
I can't come through that again.
I can't just stay here and do nothing.
Hey, he's right, Inko.
The kindest thing we could do right now is just say nothing and see him off.
I think we ought to be worrying about ourselves right about now.
Come on, we gotta face it.
Compared to Inaho, our odds of survival are probably lower.
Oh, get real!
It just so happens I'm an ace too!
Huh?
I appreciate you both.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Everyone will make it back.
That's what my left eye tells me.
Master switch on.
Fuel cell batteries heating.
Confirm voltage.
Pump is on.
Accumulator.
Pressure check.
Force feedback checking program.
Initiate.
Ejection seat functional.
IFF confirmed.
Tactical data link activated.
All systems green.
Mustang Zero-Zero.
Ready.
Hello, Grandfather.
Grandfather.
Grandfather, it is I.
It is a Salem.
Do you recognize me?
Oh, a Salem.
You look well.
I am quite weary.
How are things going for you with our subjugation of the Earth?
I have come to you today to ask a favor regarding that.
I would like you to declare a truce with the Earth.
Please issue an order commanding the Orbital Knights to immediately cease combat.
I cannot.
I will not.
But, Grandfather, why?
Earth can never be forgiven.
Do not let up on the attack.
Bring that world under our rule.
Grandfather, why is it that you hate the Earth so?
Kill Zaria, where is he?
Tell me, what has become of my son?
Conquer the Earth.
Conquer it without delay.
Father passed away years ago.
During Heaven's fall.
Wretched, filthy Terrans.
You killed him.
You killed my son.
You even killed my granddaughter.
Sweet child to Salem.
I am right here.
I am here.
Verse.
The name the ancients used when speaking of this world.
That is the title they gave to the planet Mars.
Oh, Grandfather.
Rejoice, rejoice, I say.
I have discovered a Martian super-science.
The ancients used the name Alt-Noah.
A magnificent tool to help mankind make even greater strides.
You see, Alt-Noah, is the technology we dreamed of, bringing happiness to mankind.
Yes.
It is a great power.
It must not ever be misused.
Nurture it with care.
I will.
Why, who is that standing there?
Is that a Salem?
How you have grown, my child.
You've grown beautiful.
You'll make a wonderful princess.
Lead our people to a happy and prosperous future.
Yes.
Cloncain.
I require your resources at my disposal.
Your position and connections.
Yes.
Of course, gladly.
I thank you for your loyalty.
Count Kruteo.
Come and die, you Martian bastard!
Glory to first!
What the hell is that?
Slice them all!
Go, my servants!
Wipe them out!
Open all channels.
I wish to address every Orbital Knight.
Yes, my lord.
Hear my words.
The final all-out battle for Earth has begun.
Attention, all Orbital Knights in the satellite belt and down on the surface.
Launch your attacks against the UFV from all locations at once.
This is now the time to demonstrate our vast power to the Terrans once again and show all the UFV the resistance in-
Attention, Orbital Knights.
Princess Asalem.
I am the first and rightful princess of the Empire of Verse.
Asalem vs. Ellusia.
This conflict began with but a single spark and has grown into a massive and terrible war.
Listen to that.
Another pirate broadcast?
Being transmitted on all bands, Captain.
Mm-hmm.
The conflicting hopes and dreams of many different people have resulted in a great tragedy.
This is so sad and awful for everyone.
In addition to my grief over this war, I feel both shame and a deep regret over our use of power, for which mankind was not ready.
And so, I hereby...
...declare my succession to the Imperial Throne and take my place as Empress of the Verse Empire.
And also, I will be taking as my lawful husband, Count Cruteo of the Orbital Knights.
And as the Imperial Family of Verse, we wish to make peace with Earth.
You're next time.
nika
you
ゆ
See you next time.